[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Shadow Punisher]
[Divine Constable Tally]
[Episode 5]
You're also a girl working here?
[Divine Constable Tally]
You does look beautiful.
This is interesting.
Your Star-Gathering Pavilion
is quite creative.
How dare you!
I never draw my sword
against those who don't draw their weapons.
[Yan Zige, No.1 Martial Arts Master of Northern Kun]
But if you offend Mr. Wen,
then I will
have to make an exception.
You Northern Kun people
really have a lot of rules.
You're so sharp-eyed.
This Star-Gathering Pavilion
is really something.
What a coincidence.
We Great Shi people also have our own rules.
Even if you are from Northern Kun,
within the borders of the Shi Empire,
you must obey the laws of Great Shi.
Under the laws of Great Shi,
those who violate the law and refuse to obey
shall be executed.
Lord Constable Ghost,
the Crown Prince is of noble birth.
If by any chance
he gets hurt by vulgar people like us, it'll inevitably harm
the diplomatic relations between our two states.
It's not worth it.
The Crown Prince of Northern Kun?
Who on earth are you?
How could you recognize my identity?
Your Highness, you're wise and mighty,
with a majestic bearing,
like a god descending from heaven.
Seems like
our Crown Prince wasn't exaggerating
when he talked about you.
Your Crown Prince?
Are you talking about
the incumbent Crown Prince of Great Shi,
Zhou Tiao?
Yes.
Your Highness,
I am Li Si.
This Star-Gathering Pavilion
is run by me.
I am fortunate
to have won our Crown Prince's favor
and often serve His Highness by his side.
Li Si, Young Master Qingyang,
the one highly favored by the Crown Prince of Great Shi.
Your Highness, if you don't mind,
I will clear out
all the other guests right away
and reserve all rooms
exclusively for the Northern Kun delegation.
Everyone at the Star-Gathering Pavilion
will serve you only, Your Highness.
How does that sound?
Alright,
I will show some respect for Zhou Tiao and the Divine Constable Bureau
today.
Let's go!
That was really a close call.
Yet
what a pity.
If the Crown Prince of Northern Kun
could stay at my Star-Gathering Pavilion
for one night
or casually write some calligraphy for us,
wouldn't I make a fortune from it?
My Lord, My Lady,
I remained neither servile nor arrogant just now.
I didn't bring shame upon our Great Shi, did I?
The message from our bureau
only mentioned
the visit of the Northern Kun delegation.
Master Li, how did you know
that the visitor was their Crown Prince?
It seems that
I really need to interrogate you properly back in the bureau.
To think there's someone in this world
with better sources of information than the Divine Constable Bureau.
I'm flattered.
As the saying goes,
money makes the world go round.
I just have
a few more people
working for me.
Let's head back to Tianhuang City.
Leaving so soon?
Master!
Wait...
-We'll give a 50% discount here today. -Where are you going, Master?
Master, when will you come back?
Master!
What's your take on Wenbu's visit
to our capital?
Northern Kun and Great Shi remain in a tense
and dangerous standoff at the border.
Visiting at this moment, Crown Prince Wenbu
probably harbours ulterior motives.
If his visit were for state affairs,
he could have just stayed at the official posthouse.
Why would he intend to stay at Star-Gathering Pavilion?
Moreover,
when he saw me expose his identity,
he left immediately.
As a dignified Crown Prince,
what exactly was he afraid of?
Keep an eye on him. I'll go after that one.
Okay.
A trick to get me away from there...
Master.
Master!
Master...
Channel your qi.
Channel your qi!
How many times have I told you
to never use the Arrogant Dragon Thousand-Mechanism Formation?
Don't you know how great the damage
it'll cause to your body?
Also, you have a heart condition now!
Are you courting death?
Channel your qi!
Swallow it!
If you want to die,
just tell me,
and I won't save you again.
How did I get
a disciple like you?
Be gentle.
I'm healed up. I've got my strength back.
My old bones can't take it.
You consumed a great deal of inner power
to heal my injury just now.
Let me attend to you more.
When you were 8,
it only took
15 minutes to suppress
your illness.
When you were 16,
it became one hour and a half.
Now look at you.
It takes a couple of hours every time,
and I might not even be able to hold it back.
I don't really mind.
I'm more worried about you
getting old
and weak,
with impure inner power.
What if you
end up dying from exhaustion
before the illness kills me?
It's rare
that you brat actually care about me.
Why does it sound off
to me?
What?
You think I'm not as strong as I used to be,
huh?
Brat, you're getting too bold,
aren't you?
Listen!
Your master is still your strong master!
Rub it yourself.
What? I can't call you out?
Back then,
I got this heart-burning disease
shortly after you
ran into me and took me in.
Strangely enough,
I contracted it
rather peculiarly.
The world sees plenty more peculiar things.
Master,
when you found me back then,
did you really not see
any puppet dolls?
How many times have I told you?
No!
And I've never heard of
any puppet doll,
except from you.
Hasn't that Spice-Refining Case been solved?
Didn't you find out anything?
I didn't get any answers from them.
However,
I did find a clue
related to the Kingdom of Liluo.
Liluo?
I've heard of it.
Didn't it fall long ago?
Just because it fell,
it's hard to investigate.
Now,
be it the Kingdom of Liluo
from 47 years ago
or the Mulan Hunting Ground
from 17 years ago,
there's no way to investigate them.
It seems that
there's only one way to go.
There's no way at all.
Listen,
Li Si,
do not ever mess with Tianshu Pavilion.
Those two persistent guys are coming after us.
I'm warning you one last time,
Li Si.
If you still don't listen to me,
I won't look after you anymore!
I'm leaving.
I was exhausted
from traveling for days.
So I
washed my face just now.
Where's your accomplice?
Mr. Meng, what are you saying?
I only washed my face.
Do I need an accomplice for that?
My Lord, My Lady,
would you like to wash your faces too?
[Tianhuang City, the capital of the Shi Empire]
Don't push!
One at a time, okay?
One at a time!
Don't push!
One...
Aren't we traveling incognito?
[Zhou Tiao, the Crown Prince of the Shi Empire]
Why do I feel like these lowly commoners
have all recognized me, the Crown Prince?
[Zhao Shanlei, the eunuch in charge]
Your Highness!
As handsome,
spirited,
and full of regal bearing as you are,
you can't hide it even if you try.
Everyone! Everyone!
I, the Crown Prince...
Young Master.
I, the Young Master,
am just out today
to observe the lives of the people.
Given the way you are, it's not easy
-to make people not recognize you. -I am so happy
to see
your businesses all thriving.
Don't rush.
One at a time.
One at a time!
-Young Master, mine... -One at a time.
What is this?
This is a large meat pancake
from my century-old shop.
Buy some.
Okay.
Hold on.
Delicious.
Buy all of these.
He wants them.
As well as the shop.
Buy his shop.
Buy his shop?
Hire him, too,
and have him cook in my mansion.
Thank you, Young Master!
Wait...
I'll go arrange it right away!
Young Master, have a taste!
Young Master, give it a try!
The Young Master bought my entire shop
and also hired me!
Has the Crown Prince
never even eaten a sesame pancake?
The sesame pancakes the Crown Prince eats
are always taken back,
cut into pieces, and decorated with flowers.
How would he know what a whole sesame pancake
looks like?
We don't have enough money.
How can we not have enough money?
Your Highness,
every time you travel incognito
and take a liking to something,
you just pay and take both the people
and their shops away with you.
If you keep this up,
even mountains of gold and silver
will be emptied.
You good-for-nothing.
Why does Qingyang
never run out of money?
Where is Qingyang?
How come I've heard
that he is wanted?
That's right.
The Divine Constable Bureau
issued a notice a few days ago.
Young Master Qingyang
is a suspect in the case of refining the Spice with young girls.
I guess he just ran away.
I've also heard that
the real culprit has already been executed
by the Divine Constable Bureau in Dougu County.
It's said that you, Young Master Qingyang,
are well acquainted with the Crown Prince.
If the Crown Prince sees Li Si,
I'm afraid it will cause unnecessary trouble.
That's right. Let's leave now.
I guess he will be back
in just a few days.
I can't wait a few days.
I want my cash cow
right now!
If you can't even bring me money,
aren't you a good-for-nothing?
You...
The cash cow is back.
Make way! Make way!
Qingyang!
Eunuch Zhao.
-Eunuch Zhao. -Eunuch Zhao.
Young Master Qingyang,
we need your help urgently.
One at a time.
-One at a time. Everyone has a chance. -Young Master!
We've got the banknotes!
Easy, easy.
Don't push! Don't push!
Everyone, step back a bit.
One at a time!
[Star-Gathering Pavilion]
Master.
[Wind and Moon]
To toast the Crown Prince,
I must do it myself, of course.
You have to play a long game for a big catch.
I'm looking for the truth,
for an answer.
And the one inside
may very well be
the answer I'm looking for.
Eunuch Zhao,
the Divine Constable Bureau answers directly to His Majesty.
Not even the imperial family
or nobles
can interfere with our investigations.
Li Si is currently a suspect caught by the Divine Constable Bureau.
If His Highness
shows favoritism and covers up for him,
it will inevitably put His Majesty in a difficult position.
That won't happen.
If Qingyang
really committed a crime,
as strict and impartial as His Highness is,
he will never cover up for a criminal.
♪ Have you not seen? ♪
♪ Worldly fame is like frost on the tiles ♪
♪ Gold pearls are bitter cold ♪
♪ A dream of traveling thousands of miles ♪
♪ The sun sets before the millet is ripe ♪
♪ Purple python robes on Zhuque Street ♪
♪ Tonight, the previous dynasty is buried in the new graves ♪
♪ Longquan Sword severs the net of fame and fortune ♪
♪ Cast the bright moon from my sleeve into the open sky ♪
Bravo!
Bravo.
Your Highness,
the song, "Worldly Fame," I just sang
conveys the idea that power and wealth
are just like fleeting clouds.
Don't fight for them; don't be obsessed with them.
Hurry, pour the wine.
[Peace of Mind]
Qingyang,
you are so serious all of a sudden,
just like those from the Divine Constable Bureau.
I don't like it.
Let's drink.
Speaking of the Divine Constable Bureau,
Your Highness,
please help me seek justice.
[Peace of Mind]
Everyone knows that
I'm on your side, Your Highness.
I solved the case of refining the Spice with young girls.
The people of Great Shi
are all deeply grateful to you, Your Highness.
Even though I did
make a tiny mistake,
my merits could make up for it.
Don't you think so?
You are wrong.
Am I?
Of course you are wrong!
I wasn't talking about you.
I mean,
what did you do wrong?
Look at me.
Those imperial censors
always accuse me
of being a spendthrift,
living a life of debauchery,
without holding back.
But little do they know that I, the Crown Prince,
represent the imperial family's honor.
Even if I
spend a little
too much
or make a small mistake,
there's no need
to make such a fuss,
right?
Your Highness,
you are also wrong.
Am I?
Only flowing water
is considered living water.
And money
is just like water.
If the future emperor
doesn't know how to spend money,
how can he make money?
Therefore,
you did nothing wrong.
I just love your sweet talk.
[Imperial City, Yuque]
Your Majesty,
Prince Wenbu of Northern Kun and his envoys
are resting 6 miles
away from Tianhuang City,
waiting for your summons.
Just handle it according to the rules.
Understood.
Your Majesty, the Divine Constable Bureau...
Go ahead.
The Divine Constable Bureau asked the Ministry of Revenue for more funds,
saying that the original Chunsheng Pavilion
is no longer big enough,
and they need to expand Tianshu Pavilion.
Xiazhang Tower also needs renovation.
Next year, they will also renovate Qiushou Pavilion
and Dongcang Residence.
Did the Grand Secretariat say anything?
Grand Secretary Bai has already drafted the approval document,
just waiting for your approval and signature, Your Majesty.
[Emperor Shide of the Shi Empire]
Reject it.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
the Chief Censor submitted 2 memorials.
Let her read.
One is from the Ministry of Rites, saying that
the garden recently renovated by the Crown Prince
has 72 door nails,
overstepping the limits.
The other is from the Ministry of Personnel,
dismissing 13 officials,
all of whom work for the First Prince.
The Ministry of Personnel is in the charge of the Crown Prince,
while the Ministry of Rites is overseen by the First Prince.
The two sides are fighting.
What's your take on it?
The Three Secretariats and Six Ministries of the Shi Empire
all belong to you, Your Majesty.
Oh, Shan...
But right now,
I
do need some "water."
I hope you, Young Master Qingyang,
will be willing to lend me a hand.
Your Highness, I wonder which shop
you've taken a fancy to again this time.
I will buy the whole street
for you.
The Divine Constable Bureau.
Although I am in charge of the Ministry of Revenue,
the funds need documents drafted by the Grand Secretariat,
approved and signed by my father, His Majesty.
Strange enough, in recent years,
the funds
for the Divine Constable Bureau
have never been approved.
I suppose everyone in the Divine Constable Bureau
must have quite a few complaints
about me, the Crown Prince.
Recently, I heard that
my eldest brother
sent some money
to the Divine Constable Bureau in private.
He is clearly
going against me.
Your Highness,
you and the First Prince are brothers.
Why
do you have to keep fighting like this?
Brothers?
I have no brothers.
No brothers.
They accepted
my eldest brother's money.
Do you think
they'll accept the money
I give them?
I heard that
the pair of stone lions at the gate of the Divine Constable Bureau
haven't been repaired for years.
That's why I said
everyone in my Eastern Palace
put together
is still nowhere near as smart as you,
Young Master Qingyang.
However,
sending banknotes is way too conspicuous.
How about I send a person over there?
Instead of sending money and giving people an excuse to accuse me,
it's better to send you, the God of Wealth,
over there.
I wouldn't dare.
What kind of place is the Divine Constable Bureau?
How perilous is it to work there?
Even if
one becomes the Chief of it,
it's still
not an easy job.
Why was the former Chief,
Lu Chong, dismissed?
Wasn't it because
he was incompetent?
You know nothing.
His Majesty dismissed
Lu Chong in order to cover things up...
Anyway, just don't worry.
The Divine Constable Bureau is
ranked above all the Secretariats and Ministries.
As long as
it doesn't involve imperial affairs,
everything will be very safe.
So, Your Highness, you mean
Lu Chong was dismissed
because of imperial affairs?
Could it be
the incident from 17 years ago...
Shut up!
Asking about that, do you want to die?
I've got nothing to do with that incident.
How would I know?
Yes, yes.
If you don't want to talk about it,
I won't bring it up again.
This is a toast to you, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
since you want me to join the Divine Constable Bureau,
I am willing to do my best for you.
It's just that
I am still under arrest now...
I've got your back.
What's there to be afraid of?
From now on,
you are not only my cash cow,
but also my eyes
in the Divine Constable Bureau.
Your Highness,
it's almost noon.
We need to take Li Si
back to the Divine Constable Bureau.
[Star Room]
Pardon us.
Your Highness,
we are ordered to take Li Qingyang back
to the Divine Constable Bureau for questioning.
Pardon our intrusion.
Your Highness,
where is Li Si?
How dare you!
Are you
questioning the Crown Prince?
Eunuch Zhao.
Are they asking
where Li Qingyang is?
Yes,
Your Highness.
But I
have never seen Li Qingyang.
Neither have I.
How baffling!
You are wise, Your Highness.
So wise!
It's not that I don't have money for you.
I didn't give you funds on purpose.
Do you know why?
Waters too clear hold no fish.
I deliberately cut
your Divine Constable Bureau's funding
to make you complain about being poor.
Look,
hasn't someone
rushed to offer timely help?
Who are they?
The First Prince is one.
I think the Crown Prince is also restless.
One sent money.
What about the other?
What did he send?
The Crown Prince wanted to send someone
into the Divine Constable Bureau.
Who?
Young Master Qingyang, Li Si.
This person is pretty talented at making money.
In 3 years since he entered the business,
he has opened branches
of his Star-Gathering Pavilion all over Great Shi.
Rumor has it that
this person is a suave gentleman
who spends money like water,
hits it off with the Crown Prince,
and is very close to His Highness.
His age and birthplace
remain unknown.
It was only in the 20th year of Hongyun
that the record
of his household registration appeared at the border.
[Guo Anbang, Head Eunuch]
The 20th year of Hongyun?
Continue.
Moreover,
he once broke into Tianshu Pavilion in secret.
He was also a suspect in the case of refining the Spice
with young girls.
A suspect?
You didn't arrest him?
It was a misunderstanding.
Later, Young Master Qingyang, as a commoner,
helped our bureau find the real culprit.
Do as you see fit.
Yes,
Your Majesty.
Shan.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Since your elder sister passed away,
among my peers,
apart from Grand Secretary Bai,
you're the only one
I can truly talk to.
From now on, when there are just the two of us,
feel free to speak your mind.
Don't be so distant with me, okay?
Understood.
The 20th year of Hongyun...
[Shangfang Drum] [Divine Constable Bureau]
Sir,
standing before the Shangfang Drum,
do you have any grievance to air?
Legend has it
that in the Shi Empire,
[Shangfang Drum]
from imperial family
to commoners,
[Shangfang Drum] [Divine Constable Bureau]
no matter what grievance one has,
as long as they beat this Shangfang Drum,
the Divine Constable Bureau
will solve their problems
and seek justice for them.
Three beats of the drum, and your plea will reach His Majesty.
May I ask
who you are, lady?
And what's your relationship with the Divine Constable Bureau?
What brings you
to the Divine Constable Bureau, young man?
I'd like
to join the Divine Constable Bureau.
[Shangfang Drum] [Divine Constable Bureau]
-Chief. -Chief.
Li Qingyang,
you recognized me long ago,
yet you called me lady.
How shameless.
So,
Chief,
you also knew my identity long ago.
[Divine Constable Bureau]
I am Li Si, a commoner.
Greetings, Chief of the Divine Constable Bureau,
Lady Xuanyuan.
You are a prisoner.
Where are your shackles?
[Law Prevails]
Chief,
I have long heard that the Divine Constable Bureau
safeguards the peace and security
of Great Shi
as the pillar of the state.
Thanks to
the instructions of Constable Ghost
and Constable Frost
along the way,
I admire the Divine Constable Bureau deeply.
I wish to join the Divine Constable Bureau
to serve the state.
I hope you will grant my wish, Chief.
Since the establishment of the Divine Constable Bureau,
the selection criteria have been extremely harsh.
Not only must they be absolutely loyal,
with both brains and brawn,
but more importantly,
they must have clean backgrounds.
This condition alone
can leave you unqualified, Young Master Qingyang.
What makes you think
you can join the Divine Constable Bureau?
Back in Dougu County,
I joined hands with the two constables
to solve the Moluo Flower Case,
which could be considered
protecting the local people.
This is
somewhat a merit I've earned for myself, right?
As a commoner, you
interfered in the case managed by our Divine Constable Bureau
and secretly broke into Tianshu Pavilion.
Were it not for your little merit
of helping solve the case,
you would be in prison right now.
With your merit offsetting your fault,
let's consider the score
settled.
You may get up.
Thank you, Chief.
Since your merit has offset your fault,
on what grounds can you join the Divine Constable Bureau?
I am the Crown Prince's good friend.
As far as I know,
Chief,
you are the younger sister of the late Empress,
which makes you the Crown Prince's aunt.
Considering this relationship...
The Divine Constable Bureau is independent of the imperial court,
never influenced by personal ties.
You are just a friend of the Crown Prince.
Even the Crown Prince himself
would have to pass our assessment
to join the Divine Constable Bureau.
I believe
there's no door in the world
that can't be pushed open.
It just depends on whether you're willing
and brave enough to push.
Whatever the trial,
I am willing to take it on.
Actually,
a year's salary at the Divine Constable Bureau
can't even cover your expenses
in one night, Young Master Qingyang.
Why do you want to join
the Divine Constable Bureau?
To be honest with you,
besides
making money
and doing business,
my biggest hobby is
investigating cases.
If I hear of an unsolved case,
I just
can't sleep well or eat well
before I find the real culprit.
Therefore,
if I can join the Divine Constable Bureau,
which symbolizes the authority of the law,
be a constable,
solve cases, and catch culprits,
then I would have no regrets in this life.
Constable Ghost, Constable Frost,
what do you think?
Chief,
Li Qingyang
is indeed capable.
But I think
he is used to being an undisciplined, free spirit.
I'm afraid he can't stand
the Divine Constable Bureau's rules and regulations.
When solving cases,
he has his own unique insights.
But to join the Divine Constable Bureau,
an assessment is required.
Do you hear that?
They want to test you.
I agree.
Whoever wants to test him, set the questions.
Please bring it on, My Lord, My Lady.
Li Qingyang,
the Northern Kun delegation is about to enter the capital.
We cannot let the scoundrels
in Tianhuang City
ruin the imperial court's dignity.
The Divine Constable Bureau has imposed martial law across the city lately.
You can make your contribution.
Lady Constable Frost, do you
want me to catch a few criminals?
Don't send over
any petty criminals.
It'll be beneath your status as Young Master Qingyang.
Then please enlighten me. What kind of criminal
is not considered a petty one?
Young Master Qingyang, have you ever heard of the Underworld Market?
Constable Ghost,
tell Li Si about the Underworld Market.
Yes, Chief.
The Underworld Market in the suburbs of Tianhuang City
is the largest black market,
also known as the Ghost Market.
The vendors inside act outside the law,
selling banned drugs
and rare items.
The Divine Constable Bureau intends to purge them,
but those vendors are elusive
and extremely cunning.
I have searched for years, yet found no clues.
Lord Constable Ghost has searched for years
without finding any clues.
And, Chief,
you want me to investigate?
This is such a hard nut to crack.
Chief, I think you just
don't want me to join the Divine Constable Bureau.
I didn't ask you to catch them all.
Catching a contact
or finding some contraband goods from the Ghost Market
will be considered a pass.
Young Landlord,
is it really just a fine?
No going to jail?
It's not easy to fool
the Divine Constable Bureau.
This is way too difficult.
Lord Constable Ghost has searched for years
and hasn't found anything.
I think...
I'll probably fail this time.
Yes, they're not easy to fool.
However...
I will still
try my best
to live up to your expectations.
The things you sell
can't kill
or harm anyone.
I'll take my leave.
Don't worry!
When you're caught,
I will cover
all the fines.
Anyone willing
to play along with me
will have one year's rent waived.
I'm willing to do it!
-I'll do it! -I'll go!
Ten people at most.
Too many would look fake.
[Divine Constable Bureau]
How splendid!
Oh my goodness, look at this.
Is it made of gold?
I really wish I could touch it.
It's so grand. I've never seen anything like it.
Silence!
You! What are you doing?
Don't make any noise.
Everyone, kneel properly.
You, kneel down.
I'm already on my knees.
You're still this tall on your knees?
You should see me
when I'm standing.
Then stand up.
Kneel down!
Kneel!
It's me.
Stop blabbering. Kneel properly.
Kneel properly.
Behave yourselves
and listen to the constables.
Come clean!
Everyone must sign a guarantee
before leaving!
Chief,
although these culprits have violated the law,
their offenses are very minor.
Let's detain them for 3 days,
have them pay a ransom of 20 taels of silver
as a guarantee,
and then release them, pending summons. How's that?
Just detain... Just detain us for 3 days.
I heard that.
Silence!
I heard it.
Yes, Chief.
Go.
Go!
-Go! -Be gentle! I can walk myself!
Three days?
Three days.
Go.
Chief.
I wonder
if I caught enough
of them.
If you're not satisfied,
I can go catch some more.
I deliberately cut
your Divine Constable Bureau's funding
to make you complain about being poor.
Look,
hasn't someone rushed
to offer timely help?
I also want to see
who in the imperial court
wants to win over your Divine Constable Bureau.
If the Divine Constable Bureau wants to grasp and see into
the trends of various forces in the imperial court,
we must open a door
exceptionally for those
with ulterior motives.
Since you want to join the Divine Constable Bureau,
let me see
what kind of person you are, Li Qingyang.
I hereby admit Li Si
into the Divine Constable Bureau
as a Trainee Constable.
Chief!
No further discussion on this.
Constable Eagle,
take Constable Li
to get familiar with the environment.
Tell him all the rules and regulations
of the Divine Constable Bureau.
Yes, Chief.
Since you've joined our Divine Constable Bureau,
you must uphold justice and abide by the law.
If you break the rules,
there are regulations for punishment.
Understood.
I'll follow your instructions, Chief.